jobconsultancy.com 2007-02-09

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of Job Consultancy

jobconsultancy.com's 'Terms of Use'.

1\. We do not sell or misuse any of your private registration information like name, address or email. 

2\. We may sometimes collect some information like browser details or IP for security purposes and also those purposes which help us to provide better services to users. 

3\. You can opt out of our service at any instant of time. 

4\. It is your sole responsibility and risk to correspond with the members of this site, as we have not made any effort to establish the authenticity of the person. 

More Elaborate Information

JobConsultancy.com's commitment to maintaining your privacy   
JobConsultancy.com's Privacy Statement has been created because we value our users and recognise their right to keep personal information private. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all sites managed by JobConsultancy.com.

Collecting information on JobConsultancy.com visitors   
JobConsultancy.com collects information on our site visitors collectively including which sections of the site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-personal information. JobConsultancy.com utilises this information to improve and enhance our services by monitoring the areas on the site which are most popular to you. This aggregated information may be shared with JobConsultancy.com partners to provide them with an overview of how JobConsultancy.com visitors use the site. This is done for the purposes of providing you with the best online career management services.

IP Addresses   
JobConsultancy.com's web servers gather your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or support issues with our services. Again, information is gathered in aggregate only and cannot be traced to an individual user.

Cookies & Applets   
JobConsultancy.com uses cookies to provide you with a better experience. These cookies and applets allow you to use specific services such as JobAutoResponder (an alert service which emails your chosen jobs), auto login facility (if an user chooses that option), etc,. 

Users who do not wish to receive cookies can instruct their web browsers to refuse them. However, doing so will prevent access to some areas of the site and limit your use of some of the JobConsultancy.com services.

Third Party Measurement   
In order to better understand our users, JobConsultancy.com may use third party measurement companies' services, to assess site traffic. Tracking code is used to collect the following information on the usage of the JobConsultancy.com site:   
1\. The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on JobConsultancy.com; 2\. The number of unique visitors to JobConsultancy.com; 3\. How long these unique visitors (on average) spend on JobConsultancy.com when they do visit; and Common entry and exit points into JobConsultancy.com, etc,. 

This aggregate, non-personal information is collated and provided to JobConsultancy.com to assist in analysing the usage of the site. This data is also accessible by media organisations and research companies, for the purpose of conducting industry comparisons with other Internet websites.

Collecting information on JobConsultancy.com Registered 'My Account' Members   
As part of registering with JobConsultancy.com, we collect personal information about you in order for you to take full advantage of JobConsultancy.com's services. To do this it may be necessary for you to provide additional information to JobConsultancy.com as detailed below.

Registration   
Registration is completely optional. However, registration for 'My Account' services allows you to take advantage of more of the tools and resources that assist you in finding a job. Registration includes submitting your email address. You may access and update the information through the various buttons available in the 'My Account' section of the site

Auto Match Responder   
Auto Match Responder is a service which delivers the latest job matches to the candidates and the latest matching list of candidates to employers and consultants. This service can be cancelled at any instant of time through the 'My Account' section.

Resumes   
As part of the online job service, JobConsultancy.com provides registered members with the option of creating a resume to use for application. Your registration information and email is not disclosed unless you respond to a response from the person who contact you. At the same time, email address of the responder is definately disclosed to the person to whom the responder responds. 

Private JobConsultancy.com Resumes   
All information provided when creating these resumes including name, address, email address, telephone numbers, employment and educational history are used for the purposes of facilitating your job JobConsultancy.coming efforts.   
Users can modify or delete their resume at any time by going to the 'My Account' area of the site.

Online Applications   
Making an online application to a job advertisement on JobConsultancy.com is a free and optional service that does not require registration when it is not emailed, but requires registration when an application has to be emailed to the employer or the consultant. Job applications require you to complete mandatory fields (first name, last name, phone and email) so that the advertiser can identify and contact you. Your application, including attachments and cover letters, are forwarded directly on to the third party advertiser. This information may also be disclosed to JobConsultancy.com's service providers and contractors from time to time who assist us to deliver our products and services. 

By applying to a position advertised on JobConsultancy.com you are requesting that JobConsultancy.com pass the information to the Advertiser as a part of your application. 

Additionally, you have the right to request your personal information direct from Advertisers on JobConsultancy.com.

Email communications from JobConsultancy.com   
JobConsultancy.com also provides you with selected information about job seeking and career-related topics in our email newsletter JobConsultancy.com News Update. This free service is sent to registered users and provides the option of opting out of receiving these by changing your preferences in 'My Account'. JobConsultancy.com may also make you aware of additional products and services which form part of your relationship with JobConsultancy.com.

Storage & Security of Personal Information   
JobConsultancy.com takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our system. JobConsultancy.com allows you to access your information at any time to keep it accurate and up to date. Any information which we hold for you is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. 

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by JobConsultancy.com. However, JobConsultancy.com will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information. 

You can also play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any password and accounts used on the JobConsultancy.com site. Please notify us immediately at help@JobConsultancy.com.com, if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.

JobConsultancy.com Partners , Advertisers , Employers & Consultants   
JobConsultancy.com provides links and passes online application to third party sites. The use of your information by these third party sites is not within the control of JobConsultancy.com and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of these companies. Advertisers who place job ads on JobConsultancy.com are asked to comply with Indian Information Technology Act of 2000's privacy policy with regard to their own information handling practices.   
You may also directly contact advertisers to request access to any personal information that you have sent as part of an application.

Transborder data flows   
Sometimes, we transfer information to persons outside India (e.g. a contractor located in the USA who provides us with services). By giving us your personal information, you consent to such disclosures. In addition, we believe that the recipients of such information are subject to a law, binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the information.

Feedback   
JobConsultancy.com welcomes ideas and feedback about all aspects of the site. JobConsultancy.com stores feedback that users send to us. This feedback will be used to administer and refine the service and may be shared with JobConsultancy.com partners either in aggregate form or with specific identifying characteristics removed.

Privacy & Site Changes   
From time to time, JobConsultancy.com may review and update its privacy statement. Revised versions will be updated on the website.

Contact Us   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with JobConsultancy.com, you can contact us at userhelp@JobConsultancy.com.com. Regards 

Webmaster,  jobconsultancy.com.

For more details, you can mail us at webmaster@jobconsultancy.com.
